casino440.com 2015-12-19

# Casino privacy text - playing for real money or free in casino 440

#### Casino 440 recommends

 **1\. PURPOSE OF THIS POLICY**

>  **1.1** This document describes the information collection and disclosure practices of the Web Site, owned by the 440 Group NV (Registration No. 126068 to the Game Regulatory Authority of Curacao), 440 Media Group Ltd and Casino 440, Poker 440, Bingo 440, Slots 440 and Roulette 440 (individually and collectively referred to as "the Operator").
> 
>  **1.2** Your use of the Website and any content or applications available on it will be called the "Services". 

**2\. USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

>  **2.1** Your personal information (ie, information about you by which you may be personally identified, such as name, address, phone number or email address, known in this Privacy Policy as "Your Information"), will be processed by the Operator (including their agents and employees), and (as appropriate) by our partners and subcontractors in order to provide a wide range of services. Your information will be collected when you register to open an account with us, or when you send us a written inquiry.
> 
>  **2.2** While the Web sites may contain links to other Web sites operated by third parties, the Operator is not responsible for the practices relating to the privacy or content of any such websites.
> 
>  **2.3** By using any of the Services, you agree that you have read and agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy and, by providing your information (including, for the avoidance of doubt, your a query through one of the web sites, or if you have completed the registration process of your account only partially), you consent to the use of such information by the Operator (and our partners and subcontractors) for the purposes set out in paragraph 3 of this Privacy Policy.
> 
>  **2.4** If you do not wish to provide your information under the provisions of this Privacy Policy, you should not enter the relevant information in the spaces provided for such purpose in the corresponding section in any of the Websites, or provide any personal information over the phone. However, unless you provide such information, you may not be allowed to use in full the relevant part of the Services.
> 
>  **2.5** As part of the registration process for your account, we also offer visitors registering with us the opportunity to choose not to be kept informed about future events, offers and promotions from the Operator. Visitors who wish to opt for this option must "uncheck" the appropriate box on the registration process. You can update your marketing preferences at any time under "My Account / Update Marketing Preferences" (or similar) on the Web Site (if that option is available) or by contacting the Customer Service. If, when the option is available, you have opted to receive information about upcoming events, offers and promotions by text messages to mobile phones, you will have the option to stop receiving such information at any time by replying with the word "STOP ".

 **3\. TYPE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED AND USE**

>  **3.1** The Operator will collect your information in order to:
>
>>  **3.1.1** Be able to open Your Account for you to use all the features of our Services, including, among others, add fund to your account, place bets and play games;
>> 
>>  **3.1.2** Receive your questions and comments through our Online Support Center, and answer them;
>> 
>>  **3.1.3** Comply with all applicable regulations regarding Your registration, for example, verification of age; and
>> 
>>  **3.1.4** (Provided you do not choose to be excluded from this option), keep you informed about future events, offers and promotions from the Operator.
> 
>  **3.2** In addition to a broad object identified in paragraph 3.1 above, the Operator will only use Your Information, including sharing Your Information with our partners and subcontractors who process data (including, where appropriate, Your Information) on our behalf, to:
>
>>  **3.2.1** open, operate and manage Your Account; 
>> 
>> **3.2.2** provide all the services that you request and for any other purpose related to the provision of such services;
>> 
>>  **3.2.3** verify the accuracy of your information, including the disclosure of such information to third parties, including financial institutions and age verification agencies and credit reports, to that purpose. We will keep a record of the verification and such third parties may use the information to assist other companies for verification purposes);
>> 
>>  **3.2.4** compile statistics regarding use of the Services by you and other customers;
>> 
>>  **3.2.5** develop and display material and appropriate individualized marketing content;
>> 
>>  **3.2.6** periodically send to account holders written communications to announce important service changes, updates on technical issues and changes to the Terms of Use (including this Privacy Policy);
>> 
>>  **3.2.7** fulfill our duties, obligations and regulatory responsibilities under the Gambling Act 2001, before the Regulatory Authority of Curacao, and in accordance with applicable law and with appropriate regulatory agencies in other jurisdictions where the Operator develops a regulated activity;
>> 
>>  **3.2.8** meet legal requirements, or to take measures to protect the interests of sporting bodies or other relevant agencies; 
>> 
>> **3.2.9** investigate the suspected unlawful, fraudulent or inappropriate activities in relation to the Services;
>> 
>>  **3.2.10** report a criminal offense or suspicion, including money laundering or fraud of any kind, and
>> 
>>  **3.2.11** all other purposes necessary to fulfill our contractual obligations to you.
> 
>  **3.3** The Operator will not send you unsolicited information regarding commercial offers or third party publicity.
> 
>  **3.4** The Operator may use Your username and / or first name and region for advertising or promotional purposes.
> 
>  **3.5** Phone calls made or received by our Customer Service Department may be recorded for training and security purposes.
> 
>  **3.6** We may transfer Your information in case of transfer or sale of our business or part of it, including in the event of insolvency.
> 
>  **3.7** If at any time you wish to cease our activity processing your information for the purposes listed above, please contact us and we will take the appropriate steps to comply with your request. You should be aware that the decision may involve the closure of Your Account.

 **4\. INFORMATION TRANSFER ABROAD**

>  **4.1** Within the context of the provision of services, the Operator may need to transfer information (including, Your Information) to: 
>
>> **4.1.1** other companies within the same group of companies as the Operator, and
>> 
>>  **4.1.2** our partners and subcontractors located in their home countries

 **5\. INFORMATION UPDATE**

>  **5.1** You may update or delete your information at any time from your account using the "My Account / Update my account" option (if available), or by contacting the Customer Service Department.
> 
>  **5.2** You may obtain a copy of Your information held by the Operator by contacting the Customer Service. We require to be notified in advance of up to THIRTY (30) days to fulfill your request.

 **6\. CONTACT**

>  **6.1** If at any time you feel that the Operator has not complied with the principles contained in this Privacy Policy, you can contact the Customer Service, and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to determine and correct the problem as soon as possible.
> 
>  **6.2** Effective Date of this Privacy Policy: June 1, 2012.

 **7\. DIRECTORY**

>  **(i)** European Guidelines 95/46 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data. 
> 
> **(ii)** European Guidelines 2002/58 on privacy and electronic communications, and any applicable local rule for this purpose in relation to electronic marketing in the European Union. 
> 
> **(iii)** CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 (Public Law 108-187) of the United States in relation to electronic marketing in the United States. 
> 
> **(iv)** Organic Law on Data Protection 15/1999 applicable in Spain.
